A Guide to the Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac Railroad Records, 1834-1997
Library of Virginia
- Appendix A: Oversize Folders, Contents and Location
  - Copy of the Records of the Proceedings of the Orphan's Court of Baltimore City, 9 May 1882 (Oversize 344:33)
  - Copy of the Records of the Proceedings of the Orphan's Court of Baltimore City, 11 Aug 1882 (Oversize 344:33)
  - R.F. & P. R.R., Change of Line between 20 Mile Post and Little River, Line D, 1902 (Oversize 344:34)
  - Two bonds, lost and paid cash in 1895; found and returned in 1902 (Oversize 344:34)
  - R.F. & P. R.R., James River Branch, Proposed Revision Grove Road to James River Bridge, 1905 (Oversize 344:34)
  - Plan of Proposed Crossing of the R.F. and P. and R. and P. R.R. Con. Co. [Richmond and Petersburg R.R. Connection Co.] by R. and A. R.R. [Richmond and Alleghany R.R. Co.], 1880 (Oversize 344:34)
  - Deed 1043, Washington Southern R.Y. Co. (Oversize 344:35)
  - List of Stockholders of the R.F. & P. R.R., 20 Nov 1905 (Box-folder 344:35)
  - Washington & Fredericksburg Streamboat Co., Dividend Warrants, $100 and $500, 1848 (Oversize 344:36)
  - Map of the Alexandria and Fredericksburg Railway in Connection with the great north and south lines, n.d. (Oversize 37, Map-case 2:15)
  - Richmond-Washington Co., Corporate Structure (Reconstruction Finance Corp., Railroad Division), 31 Dec 1939 (Oversize 37, Map-case 2:15)
  - Photograph 326: Aerial View of Union Station on West Broad St., Richmond, Va., a.k.a. Broad St. Station, Ca. 29 x 20 in. (Oversize 344:38)
  - Photograph 327: Front and Side View of Union Station on West Broad St., Richmond, Va., a.k.a. Broad St. Station, 10 x 13.5 in. (Oversize 344:38)
  - Instruction Sheet: Private Car "Berwick", Directions for Operating Heating systems (Vapor Car Heating Co., Inc.), Broadside. (Oversize 344:38)
  - $1000 Reward! Will Be Paid By The Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railraod Company...reward Poster relating to Mail Train Robbery near Aquia Creek, 12 Oct 1894, Broadside. (Box-folder 344:38)
  - Richmond, Fredericksburg & Potomac Railroad Company, One Hundred and Fiftieth Anniversary, 25 Feb 1834-25 Feb 1984, 1984, 5 copies; broadside, 19 x 25 in. (Oversize 344:39)
- Appendix B: Miscellaneous Reels: List of Contents, Misc. Reels 2161-2177
  - R.F. & P. R.R., Minute Book No. 1 1834-1838 (Reel 2161)
  - R.F. & P. R.R., Minute Book No. 2 1838-1843 (Reel 2161)
  - R.F. & P. R.R., Minute Book No. 3 1843-1850 (Reel 2161)
  - R.F. & P. R.R., Minute Book No. 4 1850-1861 (Reel 2162)
  - R.F. & P. R.R., Minute Book No. 5 1861-1869 (Reel 2162)
  - R.F. & P. R.R., Minute Book No. 6 1869-1888 (Reel 2162)
  - R.F. & P. R.R., Minute Book No. 7 1888-1910 (Reel 2163)
  - R.F. & P. R.R., Minute Book No. 8 1910-1924 (Reel 2163)
  - R.F. & P. R.R., Minute Book No. 9 1925-1939 (Reel 2164)
  - R.F. & P. R.R., Minute Book No. 10 1940-1956 (Reel 2164)
  - R.F. & P. R.R., Minute Book No. 11 1956-1974 (Reel 2165)
  - R.F. & P. R.R., Minute Book No. 12 1974-1977 (Reel 2165)
  - R.F. & P. R.R., Minute Book No. 13 1978-1981 (Reel 2165)
  - Lewis Ginter Land & Improvement Co., Minute Book 1901-1957 (Reel 2166)
  - Potomac R.R. Co., Minute Book No. 1 1869-1917 (Reel 2167)
  - R.F. & P. Transportation Co, Minute Book 1929-1939 (Reel 2168)
  - Richmond-Greyhound Lines, Inc., Minute Book 1932-1960 (Reel 2169)
  - Richmond Holding Corp., Minute Book 1957-1975 (Reel 2170)
  - Richmond Land Corp., Minute Book 1915-1954 (Reel 2171)
  - Richmond Terminal R.Y. Co., Minute Book No. 1 1916-1967 (Reel 2172)
  - Richmond Terminal R.Y. Co., Minute Book No. 2 1968-1975 (Reel 2172)
  - South Washington Land Corp., Minute Book 1957-1975 (Reel 2173)
  - Suburban Motor Coach Co., Minute Book 1928-1929 (Reel 2174)
  - Union Terminal Corp./Richmond Union Terminal Corp. 1929-1960 (Reel 2175)
  - Washington Southern R.Y. Co., Minute Book No. 1 1890-1910 (Reel 2176)
  - Washington Southern R.Y. Co., Minute Book [No. 2] 1910-1920 (Reel 2176)
  - Washington Southern T.Y. Co./R.F. & P. R.R. Co.: Advisory Board of Potomac Yard, Minute Book 1909-1925 (Reel 2177)